<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="app_name">DailyBabyTracker</string>
	<string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
	<string name="next">Следно</string>
	<string name="skip">Прескокни</string>
	<string name="start">Разбирам</string>
	
	<string name="slide_1_title"> Добре Дојдовте</string>
	<string name="slide_1_desc"> Денот на Башето Бебе на дланка</string>
	
	<string name="slide_2_title">Персонализирајте го дневниот распоред</string>
	<string name="slide_2_desc">Апликација за следење бебе за мајки што ќе ви помогне да ги персонализирате релевантните информации според дневниот распоред на вашето бебе</string>
	
	<string name="slide_3_title">Хранење</string>
	<string name="slide_3_desc">Апликацијата е одличен начин на зачувување на распоредот за Хранење!</string>
	
	<string name="slide_4_title">Aктивности</string>
	<string name="slide_4_desc">Апликацијата ќе ви помогне да ги пратите повеќето од дневните работи на новороденчето, како што се бројот на извалкани пелени, време на хранење, часови за спиење, време на дремнување и многу повеќе.</string>
	
	<string name="play_again_desc">За повторно да го видите лизгачот за добредојде, одете во Settings -> апликации -> лизгач за добредојде -> јасни податоци</string>
	<string name="play_again">Гледај Повторно</string>
	
	
	<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
	<string name="dbt_app_name">Дневен следач за бебиња</string>
	
	<!--  Login  -->
	<string name="dbt_hint_username">Име на Бебето </string>
	<string name="dbt_hint_password">Датум на раѓање </string>
	<string name="change_language">Промени Јазик</string>
	
	<string name="bdp_button_next">Следно</string>
	<string name="bdp_button_cancel">Откажи</string>
	<string name="bdp_error_password">Пасвордот мора да содржо 8 карактери.</string>
	<string name="bdp_filter_title">Филтер</string>
	<string name="bdp_search_title">Пребарување</string>
	<string name="bdp_product_title">Наслов</string>
	<string name="bdp_product_description">Секундарниот текст</string>
	
	<!--  backdrop menu labels -->
	<string name="bdp_feeding_label">Хранење/Доење</string>
	<string name="bdp_sleeping_label">Спиење</string>
	<string name="bdp_diapers_label">Менување пелени</string>
	<string name="bdp_leisure_label">Активности</string>
	<string name="bdp_growth_label">Растење/Развивање</string>
	<string name="bdp_pumping_label">Пумпање</string>
	<string name="bdp_health_label">Здравје</string>
	<string name="bdp_account_label">Мој Профил</string>
	
	<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
	<string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
	<string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
	<string name="bdp_settings_title">Поставки</string>
	<string name="table_for_nutritions">Табела за исхрана</string>
	
	<string name="title_activity_settings">Пребарување</string>
	
	<!-- Preference Titles -->
	<string name="messages_header">Пораки</string>
	<string name="sync_header">Синхронизација</string>
	
	<!-- Messages Preferences -->
	<string name="signature_title">Твој потпис</string>
	<string name="reply_title">Дефинирана акција за одговор</string>
	
	<!-- Sync Preferences -->
	<string name="sync_title">Периодично синхронизирање на е-пошта</string>
	<string name="attachment_title"> Превземање на примени податоци</string>
	<string name="attachment_summary_on">Автоматско превземање на податоци од примени е-пошти
	</string>
	<string name="attachment_summary_off">Превземи податоци само кога рачно ќе се побара</string>
	<string name="search">Пребарување</string>
	
	<string name="messages_header1">Пораки</string>
	<string name="title">Наслов</string>
	<string name="recipeId">Идентификација на рецептот</string>
	<string name="bdp_home_label">Home</string>
	<string name="sleeping_schedule_notes">Sleeping schedule notes</string>
	<string name="about_sleeping_schadule">Keep in mind that newborn schedules are generally much more variable than older children’s schedules. A baby doesn’t really get on a clock-based schedule until 6 months old, on average, though some are naturally more predictable than others.</string>
	<string name="your_baby_s_growth_first_12_months">Your baby’s growth – first 12 months</string>
	<string name="your_baby_s_growth">Your baby’s growth</string>
	
	
	<string name="growth_1st_mont">Infant development begins at at birth and they grow fast and learn a lot.
		At 1 month, cuddling, sleeping and feeding are all that really matters to your baby.
		The time you spend with them will help their brain to grow and develop as they start to experience the world.</string>
	<string name="growth_2nd_mont">Your 2-month-old is growing fast and becoming more alert.
		They will be making more sounds and getting more skilled at moving their body.
		They will still be crying a lot - but you’ve probably already seen that magic first smile (usually at 6 weeks) which somehow makes all the hard work worthwhile.</string>
	<string name="growth_3th_mont">By 3 months, your baby will have formed a strong attachment to you.
		They will respond to you with lots of smiles, and might even talk back to you in their own way.
		The worst of the crying should be nearly over, and you can really enjoy your baby as they grow into their own little person.</string>
	<string name="growth_4th_mont">From 4 months, your baby will quickly be learning to coordinate their body.
		They will have more control over what they do, their vision, touch and hearing will be much more developed, and they will start to move around much more.
		They can communicate much better too, and the number of hours for which they cry should have settled by now.</string>
	<string name="growth_5th_mont">Your baby will be growing and developing rapidly now.
		They are learning more about the world and how they fit into it. Many of the new things your baby is learning at 5 months are preparing them for eating solid food.
		It is usually recommended you introduce solids at 6 months, but some babies are ready as early as 4 months.
		So, if you think it’s time, it’s fine to start experimenting with solids now.</string>
	<string name="growth_6th_mont">Six months is an exciting time and your baby will now be developing very fast.
		The left side of their brain will have has started communicating with the right side, meaning they can coordinate their body better.
		You will be understanding your baby much better now as they let you know whether they’re happy or sad and start to respond to words</string>
	<string name="growth_7th_mont">Your baby is now growing up fast.
		They may well be sitting on their own, eating solid foods - although breastmilk or formula will still be their main source of nutrition - and understanding more about what you want from them.
		It’s an exciting time to watch them grow</string>
	<string name="growth_8th_mont">Your 8-month-old is probably getting into everything and moving around a lot as they explore the world.
		This means more work for you, but it’s wonderful to watch their fascination grow.</string>
	<string name="growth_9th_mont">At around 9 months, babies’ brains have a growth spurt.
		They will really be developing a personality now, and you’ll be getting a glimpse of the child they’re going to grow into.</string>
	<string name="growth_10th_mont">Your 10-month-old will now be very active.
		You’ll probably be chasing around after them as they crawl and pull themselves up onto furniture, and you’ll be learning more about your baby’s developing personality.</string>
	<string name="growth_11th_mont">At 11 months old, your baby will be almost a toddler, and they will be maturing fast.
		You’ll probably be surprised how quickly they can move around your home and how independent they are becoming.</string>
	<string name="growth_12th_mont">At 12 months, your baby is officially a toddler.
		If they haven’t already, it won’t be long now before they take their first steps, develop a sense of humour, and tell you they love you.</string>

</resources>